<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<!-- Map:

          [02]               beach
            |                  |
    [03]~~[01]*     customs~~harbor
            |                  |
    [05]~~[04]       hamlet~~beach

-->
<zone id="1" name="Starting Area">
    <room id="1">
        <title>
            <en_US>Recalcitrant Adventurer's Harbor</en_US>
            <pt_BR>Porto do Aventureiro Recalcitrante</pt_BR>
        </title>
        <description>
            <en_US>The port's gray sand complements its decaying look very well. Many adventurers land here daily, attracted by the stories of gold and glory. There are also many fishermen and villagers from the local village doing their jobs or trying to extract some coin from the newcomers.
The Recalcitrant Adventurer's Harbor has been the gateway for all kinds of adventurous spirits into the Realm of Shambles. Of course, this vast region does not deserve to be called a "kingdom" but, without a doubt, it well deserves the demeritable nickname of "shambles" as it is truly a lawless land. In fact, it is officially called "vastness", and there are many here who declare themselves kings and princes, or some other title.
These powers rule in city-states or small regions over which they manage to impose their authority. However, in the Realm of Shambles nothing lasts, princes fall and rise day after day.
The beach stretches from north to south, and to the east is the great sea through which adventurers arrive. To the west there appears to be a customs house.</en_US>
            <pt_BR>A areia cinzenta do porto complementa muito bem o seu aspecto decadente. Muitos aventureiros desembarcam aqui diariamente, atraídos pelas histórias de ouro e glória. Há também muitos pescadores e aldeões da aldeia local fazendo seus trabalhos ou tentando extrair alguma moeda dos recém-chegados.
O Porto do Aventureiro Recalcitrante tem sido a porta de entrada para todos os tipos de espíritos aventureiros no Reino da Balbúrdia. É claro que esta vasta região não merece ser chamada de "reino", mas, sem dúvida, merece o apelido demeritório de "balbúrdia", pois é realmente uma terra sem lei. Na verdade, é oficialmente conhecida como "vastidão", e há muitos aqui que se declaram reis e príncipes, ou algum outro título.
Essas potestades governam cidades-estados ou pequenas regiões sobre as quais conseguem impor a sua autoridade. No entanto, no Reino da Balbúrdia nada dura, príncipes caem e se levantam dia após dia.
A praia se estende de norte a sul, e a leste fica o grande mar por onde chegam os aventureiros. A oeste parece haver uma alfândega.</pt_BR>
        </description>
        <exits north="2" south="4" west="3"/>
        <spawns>
            <rose qty="1"/>
        </spawns>
    </room>
    
    <room id="2">
        <title>
            <en_US>Drowned Man's Beach</en_US>
            <pt_BR>Praia do Afogado</pt_BR>
        </title>
        <description>
            <en_US>No description.</en_US>
            <pt_BR>Sem descrição.</pt_BR>
        </description>
        <exits south="1"/>
        <spawns>
            <poo qty="1"/>
        </spawns>
    </room>
    
    <room id="3">
        <title>
            <en_US>Customs House</en_US>
            <pt_BR>Alfândega</pt_BR>
        </title>
        <description>
            <en_US>No description.</en_US>
            <pt_BR>Sem descrição.</pt_BR>
        </description>
        <exits east="1"/>
        <spawns>
            <apple qty="1"/>
        </spawns>
    </room>
    
    <room id="4">
        <title>
            <en_US>Violated Damsel's Beach</en_US>
            <pt_BR>Praia da Donzela Violada</pt_BR>
        </title>
        <description>
            <en_US>A bad name for a beach, but suitable for a sad story, never forgotten by the villagers. A reminder that not all adventurers who come to these lands are heroes. A lone tree, dry and dead, full of women's underwear swaying in the wind completes the scene.
To the north lies the harbor, to the west a hamlet can be seen.</en_US>
            <pt_BR>Um nome ruim para uma praia, mas adequado para uma história triste, nunca esquecida pelos aldeões. Um lembrete de que nem todos os aventureiros que chegam à essas terras são heróis. Uma árvore solitária, seca e morta, repleta de roupas íntimas femininas balançando ao vento completa a cena.
Ao norte encontra-se o porto, a oeste avista-se uma aldeia.</pt_BR>
        </description>
        <exits north="1" west="5"/>
        <spawns>
            <sparrow qty="1"/>
        </spawns>
    </room>
    
    <room id="5">
        <title>
            <en_US>Boot Fisherman's Hamlet</en_US>
            <pt_BR>Aldeia dos Pescadores de Bota</pt_BR>
        </title>
        <description>
            <en_US>No description.</en_US>
            <pt_BR>Sem descrição.</pt_BR>
        </description>
        <exits east="4"/>
        <spawns>
            <sword qty="1"/>
        </spawns>
    </room>
</zone>
